1. randomEmail = custom.RandomData.generateRandomEmail()
5. randomFirstName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomFirstName()
9. randomLastName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomLastName()
13. randomPhone = custom.RandomData.generateRandomPhone()
17. randomAddress = custom.RandomData.generateRandomAddress()
21. randomCode = custom.RandomData.generateRandomCode()
25. openBrowser(URL)
29. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
33. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
37. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-account"), "agungpriyadi")
41. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Password"), "Laskar123456")
45. click(findTestObject("Login/btn-sign in"))
49. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
53. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Address Management/Shipping Address/btn_My Address"), 4)
57. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Shipping Address/btn_My Address"))
61. editBtn = new com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.TestObject()
65. editBtn.addProperty("xpath", EQUALS, "(//button[contains(.,'Edit')])[1]")
69. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Shipping Address/btn_Edit"))
73. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_First Name"), 10)
77. clearText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_First Name"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
81. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_First Name"), randomFirstName)
85. clearText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_Last Name"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
89. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_Last Name"), randomLastName)
93. clearText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_Mobile Phone"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
97. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_Mobile Phone"), randomPhone)
101. clearText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_E-mail"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
105. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_E-mail"), randomEmail)
109. clearText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_Address"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
113. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_Address"), randomAddress)
117. clearText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_ZipPostal Code"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
121. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_ZipPostal Code"), randomCode)
125. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/button_Save"))
129. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Address Management/Shipping Address/lbl_Shipping Address"), 10)
133. verifyName = new com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.TestObject()
137. verifyName.addProperty("xpath", EQUALS, //*[contains(text(),'$randomFirstName')])
141. verifyElementPresent(verifyName, 10)
145. takeScreenshot()
149. comment("Email      : " + randomEmail)
153. comment("First Name : " + randomFirstName)
157. comment("Last Name  : " + randomLastName)
161. comment("Phone      : " + randomPhone)
165. comment("Address    : " + randomAddress)
169. comment("Code    : " + randomCode)
173. closeBrowser()
177. closeBrowser()